FARREL DINARTA

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

+62 813 8353 3583



farreldinarta12@gmail.com



Cluster Nirwana Blok NR I No. 10, Modernland, Cipondoh, Tangerang, Indonesia



ingenhouzs.github.io/farreldinarta/



linkedin.com/in/farreldinarta



IngenHouzs

ABOUT ME

A Junior Developer. Currently i am pursuing my Computer Science Degree while actively honing my skills through college courses and external resources. I don't have any specific field of expertise yet but currently i love to get my hands dirty on web development, especially back-end development since it can express my ideas visually.

EDUCATION

2009 - 2015

Strada Santo Fransiskus Elementary School

2015 - 2018

Strada Santa Maria 2 Junior High School

2018 - 2021

Strada Santo Thomas Aquino Senior High School

2021 - now

Multimedia Nusantara University | Computer Science

EXPERIENCES

2021 - 2022

Member of Programming Club at Multimedia Nusantara University

2022 - 2023

Financial Manager of Informatics Student Association at Multimedia Nusantara University

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

Back-end Developer on Stealth Startup (assigned on a project called AdainAcara)

Feb 2023 - now

Fullstack Developer of MRMS UMN 2023

April 2023 - now

Back-end Developer of MAXIMA UMN 2023

SKILLS

Front-end

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

ReactJS

Next.js

Back-end

PHP

Laravel

Node.js

Python

Database

MySQL

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

Others

С

C++

CERTIFICATES

October 2021

Progate Python Course

March 2022

Shopee Code League 2022 Participant

June 2022

Dicoding Indonesia - Beginner Backend Development Course

June 2022

Dicoding Indonesia - Beginner JavaScript Course